<?xml version="1.0"?>
<registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects"
                 xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                 xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.2.0/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
    <registryObject group="Seattle Proteome Center (SPC)">
        <key>MON27e5fec2-c808-410d-9b5d-b76f80c6cb66</key>
        <originatingSource>http://www.proteomebrowser.org</originatingSource>
        <collection type="dataset">
            <name type="primary">
                <namePart type="">PeptideAtlas</namePart>
            </name>
            <identifier type="local">MON27e5fec2-c808-410d-9b5d-b76f80c6cb66</identifier>
            <location>
                <address>
                    <electronic type="url">
                        <value>http://www.peptideatlas.org/</value>
                    </electronic>
                </address>
            </location>
            <description type="full">
                &lt;p&gt;PeptideAtlas is a multi-organism, publicly accessible compendium of peptides identified in a
                large set of tandem mass spectrometry proteomics experiments. Mass spectrometer output files are
                collected for human, mouse, yeast, and several other organisms, and searched using the latest search
                engines and protein sequences. All results of sequence and spectral library searching are subsequently
                processed through the&amp;nbsp; &lt;a
                href="http://tools.proteomecenter.org/wiki/index.php?title=Software:TPP" target="_blank"&gt;Trans
                Proteomic Pipeline&lt;/a&gt; to derive a probability of correct identification for all results in a
                uniform manner to insure a high quality database, along with false discovery rates at the whole atlas
                level. Results may be queried and browsed at the PeptideAtlas web site. The raw data, search results,
                and full builds can also be downloaded for other uses.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;
                &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
            </description>
            <description type="logo">
                &lt;p&gt;http://www.peptideatlas.org/images/pa_transparent_background1.gif&lt;/p&gt;
            </description>
            <description type="rights">
                It is the policy of PeptideAtlas to make publicly available for
                download as much of the raw data we use to build the PeptideAtlas as possible.
                This includes datasets that have been previously published or otherwise released
                by the data producers. If you download and use these data in a published work,
                please cite the associated article (or data contributors if unpublished); an
                acknowledgement of the PeptideAtlas repository would also be appreciated. There
                are also many unpublished raw datasets used to build the PeptideAtlas, and these
                are not made available for download until publication or release by the
                producers.
            </description>
            <relatedObject>
                <key>MON3e010934-f57b-4704-bc44-74ac32429e9d</key>
                <relation type="isOwnedBy">
                    <url/>
                </relation>
            </relatedObject>
            <relatedObject>
                <key>MONebcb3d9b-324f-47d5-9591-a6b1414823f2</key>
                <relation type="isOperatedOnBy">
                    <url/>
                </relation>
            </relatedObject>
            <subject type="anzsrc-for">030406</subject>
            <subject type="anzsrc-for">060109</subject>
            <subject type="anzsrc-for">110106</subject>
        </collection>
    </registryObject>
</registryObjects>
