<?xml version="1.0"?>
<registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects"
                 xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                 xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.2.0/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
    <registryObject group="Human Protein Atlas Consortium">
        <key>MON56dfdcd6-81df-49f1-8540-6d1809e49589</key>
        <originatingSource>http://www.proteomebrowser.org</originatingSource>
        <collection type="dataset">
            <name type="primary">
                <namePart type="">The Human Protein Atlas</namePart>
            </name>
            <identifier type="local">MON56dfdcd6-81df-49f1-8540-6d1809e49589</identifier>
            <location>
                <address>
                    <electronic type="url">
                        <value>http://www.proteinatlas.org/</value>
                    </electronic>
                </address>
            </location>
            <description type="full">
                &lt;p&gt;The Human Protein Atlas portal is a publicly available database with millions of
                high-resolution images showing the spatial distribution of proteins in 46 different normal human tissues
                and 20 different cancer types, as well as 47 different human cell lines. The data is released together
                with application-specific validation performed for each antibody, including immunohistochemisty, Western
                blot analysis and, for a large fraction, a protein array assay and immunofluorescent based confocal
                microscopy. The database has been developed in a gene-centric manner with the inclusion of all human
                genes predicted from genome efforts. Search functionalities allow for complex queries regarding protein
                expression profiles, protein classes and chromosome location.&lt;/p&gt;
            </description>
            <description type="logo">
                &lt;p&gt;http://www.proteinatlas.org/images_static/logo_text_small.gif&lt;/p&gt;
            </description>
            <description type="rights">
                The use of data and images from this site in publications and
                presentations is permitted provided that the following conditions are met: The
                publication and/or presentation are solely for informational and non-commercial
                purposes. The source of the data and/or image is referred to this site
                (www.proteinatlas.org) and/or one or more of our publications are cited.
            </description>
            <relatedObject>
                <key>MON8abe17d0-f3a3-44ff-aee3-afcbd0229d9a</key>
                <relation type="isOwnedBy">
                    <url/>
                </relation>
            </relatedObject>
            <relatedObject>
                <key>MONebcb3d9b-324f-47d5-9591-a6b1414823f2</key>
                <relation type="isOperatedOnBy">
                    <url/>
                </relation>
            </relatedObject>
            <relatedInfo type="publication">
                <identifier type="doi">doi:10.1038/nbt1210-1248</identifier>
                <title>Uhlen M, Oksvold P, Fagerberg L, Lundberg E, Jonasson K, Forsberg M, Zwahlen M, Kampf C, Wester
                    K, Hober S, Wernerus H, Bjorling L, Ponten F. Towards a knowledge-based Human Protein Atlas. Nat
                    Biotechnol. 2010 28(12):1248-50.
                </title>
                <notes/>
            </relatedInfo>
        </collection>
    </registryObject>
</registryObjects>
