<?xml version="1.0"?>
<registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects"
                 xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                 xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.2.0/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
    <registryObject group="Human Protein Atlas Consortium">
        <key>MON8abe17d0-f3a3-44ff-aee3-afcbd0229d9a</key>
        <originatingSource>http://www.proteomebrowser.org</originatingSource>
        <party type="group">
            <name type="primary">
                <namePart type="">Human Protein Atlas Consortium</namePart>
            </name>
            <identifier type="local">MON8abe17d0-f3a3-44ff-aee3-afcbd0229d9a</identifier>
            <location>
                <address>
                    <electronic type="url">
                        <value>http://www.proteinatlas.org/about/organization</value>
                    </electronic>
                    <electronic type="email">
                        <value>contact@proteinatlas.org</value>
                    </electronic>
                </address>
            </location>
            <description type="full">
                &lt;p&gt;The Swedish Human Protein Atlas project, funded by the Knut and Alice Wallenberg Foundation,
                has been set up to allow for a systematic exploration of the human proteome using Antibody-Based
                Proteomics. This is accomplished by combining high-throughput generation of affinity-purified antibodies
                with protein profiling in a multitude of tissues and cells assembled in tissue microarrays. Confocal
                microscopy analysis using human cell lines is performed for more detailed protein localization. The
                program hosts the Human Protein Atlas portal with expression profiles of human proteins in tissues and
                cells.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The main sites are located at AlbaNova and SciLifeLab, KTH - Royal Institute of Technology,
                Stockholm, Sweden, the Rudbeck Laboratory, Uppsala University, Uppsala, Sweden and Lab Surgpath, Mumbai,
                India. The main objective of the resource centre is to produce specific antibodies to human target
                proteins using a high-throughput production method involving the cloning and protein expression of
                Protein Epitope Signature Tags (PrESTs). After purification, the antibodies are used to study expression
                profiles in cells and tissues and for functional analysis of the corresponding proteins in a wide range
                of platforms. The Stockholm sites are responsible for generating high-quality antibodies and to perform
                the immunofluorescence analysis, the Uppsala site is responsible for large-scale protein profiling in
                tissues and cells using immunohistochemistry and the Mumbai site for the annotation of the
                immunohistochemistry images.&lt;/p&gt;
            </description>
            <subject type="anzsrc-for">110702</subject>
        </party>
    </registryObject>
</registryObjects>
