<?xml version="1.0"?>
<registryObjects xmlns="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects"
                 xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                 xsi:schemaLocation="http://ands.org.au/standards/rif-cs/registryObjects http://services.ands.org.au/documentation/rifcs/1.2.0/schema/registryObjects.xsd">
    <registryObject group="Monash University">
        <key>MONebcb3d9b-324f-47d5-9591-a6b1414823f2</key>
        <originatingSource>http://www.proteomebrowser.org</originatingSource>
        <service type="assemble">
            <identifier type="local">MONebcb3d9b-324f-47d5-9591-a6b1414823f2</identifier>
            <name type="primary">
                <namePart type="">The Proteome Browser</namePart>
            </name>
            <location>
                <address>
                    <electronic type="url">
                        <value>http://www.proteomebrowser.org</value>
                    </electronic>
                </address>
            </location>
            <subject type="anzsrc-for">060109</subject>
            <subject type="anzsrc-for">110106</subject>
            <description type="full">
                &lt;p&gt; The Proteome Browser is an analysis tool which
                integrates protein data from a number of proteomics and genomic data sources. It
                displays a &amp;quot;Traffic Light&amp;quot; report , where the X axis will relate
                to each gene (i.e. protein) ordered by default in the order found on the Chromosome,
                and the Y axis relates to the various protein data sources/sets.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;
                The &amp;quot;traffic light&amp;quot; system is used to indicate cases where
                different types of data exists and does not exist for a particular protein. Various
                aspects of the underlying contributing information is envisaged to be available for
                further analyses using clustering and drill down/through capabilities. The screen is
                dynamic showing relevant information according to the type of information selected
                on the Traffic Light Report and will provide links to external systems where
                appropriate.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Example analytical functions that are envisaged
                include: Hierarchical clustering of protein data on the X axis based on the
                information of the other axis (similar in function to clustering tools that are
                currently used to classify gene expression data across 10&amp;rsquo;s of
                1000&amp;rsquo;s of data points). Similar, yet directed analysis of specific
                proteins based on functional classification (e.g. only enzymes or structural
                proteins (and many subsets thereof)), disease involvement (e.g. only those
                associated with diabetes, heart disease) is also envisaged. These analysis functions
                will assist in producing a resource that will help elucidate biological and
                molecular function and advance diagnosis and treatment of diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
            </description>
            <description type="deliverymethod">
                Software
            </description>
            <description type="accessRights">
                &lt;p&gt;http://www.proteomebrowser.org/tpb/site/termsofuse.jspx&lt;/p&gt;
            </description>
            <relatedInfo type="website">
                <identifier type="uri">http://www.ozhupohpp7.com</identifier>
                <title>The Proteome Browser Project Wiki</title>
            </relatedInfo>
        </service>
    </registryObject>
</registryObjects>
